costumekingdom.com 2016-12-03

# privacy

### Our Commitment to Privacy

Costumekingdom Inc. respects our customers’ privacy and is committed to collect, maintain and use customer information responsibly. This privacy statement explains our information collection, storage, and use practices for the Costumekingdom websites and our other forms of online communication. This policy applies to Costumekingdom Inc. and its affiliated companies, including but not limited to T&T inc.

#### EFFECTIVE DATE AND CHANGES

This policy has been last updated July 13th, 2007. If this policy changes in the future, we will let you know by posting any changes in this web page or by communicating directly with you. The revised Internet Private Policy will be displayed via a link on this website so that you will know what types of information we gather.

#### WHAT KIND OF ONLINE INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We do collect some limited information about your visit but none of this information is personally identifiable to you.

#### HOW DOES COSTUMEKINGDOM USE AND SHARE MY INFORMATION?

Personally Identifiable Information. We receive and store any personally identifiable information you enter on our Web Site or give us in any other way. Specifically, we collect: (a) information you provide when registering or making purchases on the Web Site;(b) information about your transactions with Costumekingdom. We use this information to: complete your orders, send merchandise for online store purchases, contact you when necessary, send prizes to contest winners and send information about our company, including promotional material.

Costumekingdom Online Orders. When you make an online purchase from Costumekingdom, we use your information to process your order. We will send you emails to confirm your order, and we may need to contact you via phone, postal mail or email if we have other questions. In addition, you will be signed up to receive email updates. You may opt-out of receiving future electronic mailings by following the instructions outlined below.

Personal experience. In order to deliver information specific to your needs, or to make your experience more convenient, we may use your identifiable information in a number of ways on our website and in our emails. More specifically, when you enter into a contest or sweepstake or take some action on our website that requires you to enter personal information, we may also use your personal information to automatically enter data into the required fields for that contest or action.

Contests and sweepstakes: We regularly run co-sponsored contests and giveaways. Participation in these contests is completely voluntary; you have the choice whether or not to disclose information required for contest registration. Information requested may include; contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information is used to notify winners and award prizes. By participation in the contests, you agree we may use your information for marketing or promotional purposes.

#### HOW DO I OPT OUT/UNSUBSCRIBE FROM EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS?

You may unsubscribe from our email lists at any time by [clicking here](http://store.costumekingdom.com/support/helpunsubscribe.aspx?source=HOBPRIVACY) and entering the email address you used when you created the account. Please allow 2-3 business days for these changes to take effect.

#### HOW DOES COSTUMEKINGDOM PROTECT CHILDREN’S PRIVACY?

As a general audience site, we do not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under 13 without first obtaining verifiable consent from their parents. If we become aware that account holder is under 13 and has signed up without our prior verifiable parental consent, we will delete his or her account. Please visit the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 _(COPPA)_ website for more information on protecting children’s online privacy.

#### HOW DOES COSTUMEKINGDOM USE COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS?

**Cookies.** We use cookies—a small amount of data, often containing an anonymous unique identifier, sent from our computers and stored on your computer system. We use cookies on your computer for a number of purposes, including: to insure you do not see the same ad repeatedly, deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

**Web beacons.** During some visits, we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, include page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information _(such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs)_ , and methods used to browse away from the page. We use this information to help personalize your web experience and the emails we send you and to improve our products.

#### WHAT IF I HAVE QUESTIONS OR COMMENTS ABOUT THIS POLICY?

We welcome your questions or comments regarding this privacy statement. Please contact us by email or postal mail at:

**Costume Kingdom Customer Service**  
18720 Oxnard Street, #108  
Tarzana, CA 91356  

**SPECIAL NOTIFICATION FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS—YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS.**  
Individual customers who reside in California and have provided their personal information to Costumekingdom may request information about our disclosures of certain categories of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. HOWEVER YOU WILL BE INFORMED THAT WE DO NOT SHARE THIS INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES. Such requests must be submitted to us at the following address:

**Costume Kingdom**  
18720 Oxnard Street, #108  
Tarzana, CA 91356

Within thirty days of receiving such a request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right to not respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this paragraph.
